<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<data xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
      xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="reports.xsd">
    <reports>
        <report>
            <host>crimson</host>
            <description>
                Compare what expansions, seasons and dungeon keys players have to their account on Destiny 2.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>crucible</host>
            <description>
                Offers a useful and pretty way to look up achievements in Destiny 2's Crucible.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>destiny</host>
            <description>
                Historical archive of Destiny 2 API database updates and exactly what's added and changed.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>dungeon</host>
            <description>
                A summary of dungeon statistics for Destiny. Look up raid clears, speedruns, and sherpas.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>grandmaster</host>
            <description>
                Get insights about your and anyone's performance in Destiny 2's Nightfall: The Ordeal strikes
                on Grandmaster difficulty.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>guardian</host>
            <description>
                A lookup-service for opponents and (potential) teammates, no matter the gamemode.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>loot</host>
            <description>
                Check what raid, dungeon and mission-related exotic weapons your clanmates are missing on Destiny 2.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>member</host>
            <description>
                Displays clan statistics in tables and charts.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>nightfall</host>
            <description>
                Shows information about Nightfalls and offers leaderboards and stats to players.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>parallel</host>
            <description>
                Covers Guardians who contributed to Destiny 2 in a meaningful way, and have received the Parallel
                Program emblem.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>raid</host>
            <description>
                A summary of Raid statistics for Destiny. Look up raid clears, speedruns, and sherpas.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>reports</host>
            <description>
                A list of all Destiny-related .report domains.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>telesto</host>
            <description>
                Tracks time since the last Telesto bug.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>trials</host>
            <description>
                A companion for Destiny's Trials of Osiris. Look up everything on your opponents or yourself.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>triumph</host>
            <description>
                Ranks players based on their Triumph score, and offers a visually stimulating view of their personal
                in-game achievements.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>twid</host>
            <stylized_name>TWID</stylized_name>
            <description>
                Displays a link to the latest TWID and offers notifications for new TWID releases.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>seal</host>
            <description>
                Shows Seal information and related Triumph data for a given player.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>system</host>
            <description>
                Shows which Bungie API systems are currently en- or disabled.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>gm</host>
            <stylized_name>GM</stylized_name>
            <description>
                Shows info about upcoming Grandmaster Nightfalls and offers GM leaderboards for past seasons.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>d2rotations</host>
            <stylized_name>d2Rotations</stylized_name>
            <description>
                Shows various weekly and daily rotations including lost sectors, nightfalls, raid and dungeon rotators, and more.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>emblem</host>
            <description>
                Shows stats on emblem distribution among players.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>lostsector</host>
            <stylized_name>LostSector</stylized_name>
            <description>
                Shows stats on Lost Sectors, including top loadouts and player statistics.
            </description>
        </report>
        <report>
            <host>checkpoint</host>
            <description>
                24/7 checkpoint bots for popular raids and dungeons for casual and hardcore players.
            </description>
        </report>
    </reports>
</data>
